<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Numero</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="bd_text">Numerology uses a person\'s birthday to calculate his or her life path. </string>
	<string name="bd_button_text">Please Enter Birthday!!</string>
	<string name="life_path_prefix">lp</string>
	<string name="lp1">
	     <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This  person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to be independent and to stand on your own two feet, to find and do your own thing.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Attempt an undertaking that\'s never been tried before
		<br/>
		&#8226;Evelop leadership qualities, self-sufficiency, and a take-charge attitude
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="lp2">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to be a peacemaker, a diplomat.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Be sensitive to others\' feelings.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn how to please through charm, sweetness, friendliness, helpfulness, and considerration.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="lp3">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to be a gracious host or hostess.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Develop an appreciation for beauty and beautiful things.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Not scatter your energies or waste your talents.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="lp4">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn order and self-discipline.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Be the doer, the one who can be counted on to get the job done.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn the joy that comes through accomplishment, and take pride in your work.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="lp5">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn the thrill of the new and the unusual.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to be versatile and flexible.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Expect change and the unexpected.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="lp6">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Develop a sense of responsibility.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Be willing to lend your support and encouragement to those in need of it.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn the difference between helping out and meddling.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="lp7">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Obtain as good an education as possible.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Seek knowledge, think deeply, and develop intuitions.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Investigate the unknown in life.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Read between the lines and not judge by superficial appearances.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="lp8">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Develop drive and ambition.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to think big and strive for success.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn how to make, save, and accumulate money.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Develop executive talents - the capacity to manage, organize, direct, and lead.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>
		
	<string name="lp9">
	    <![CDATA[
	    <p>
	    This person with above birthday <b>needs</b> to:
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to love and serve your fellow man.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Learn to be a humanitarian.
		<br/>
		&#8226;Give others your love, sympathy, help, and understanding without thought of reward.
		</p>
		]]>
	</string>
</resources>
